[
  {
    "name": "EN-PL music instruments",
    "cards": [
      {
        "front": "bass",
        "back": "gitara basowa"
      },
      {
        "front": "the drums",
        "back": "perkusja"
      },
      {
        "front": "flute",
        "back": "flet poprzeczny"
      },
      {
        "front": "recorder",
        "back": "flet prosty"
      },
      {
        "front": "voilin",
        "back": "skrzypce"
      },
      {
        "front": "trumpet",
        "back": "trąbka"
      },
      {
        "front": "grand piano",
        "back": "skrzypce"
      },
      {
        "front": "accordion",
        "back": "akordeon"
      },
      {
        "front": "harpsichord",
        "back": "klawesyn"
      },
      {
        "front": "trombone",
        "back": "puzon"
      },
      {
        "front": "harp",
        "back": "harfa"
      },
      {
        "front": "cello",
        "back": "wiolonczela"
      },
      {
        "front": "french horn",
        "back": "waltornia"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "EN-PL Sports",
    "cards": [
      {
        "front": "basketball",
        "back": "koszykówka"
      },
      {
        "front": "archery",
        "back": "łucznictwo"
      },
      {
        "front": "alpine skiing",
        "back": "narciarstwo alpejskie"
      },
      {
        "front": "diving",
        "back": "nurkowanie"
      },
      {
        "front": "fencing",
        "back": "szermierka"
      },
      {
        "front": "basketball",
        "back": "koszykówka"
      },
      {
        "front": "football",
        "back": "piłka nożna"
      },
      {
        "front": "voleyball",
        "back": "siatkówka"
      },
      {
        "front": "figure skating",
        "back": "łyżwiarstwo figurowe"
      },
      {
        "front": "rowing",
        "back": "żeglarstwo"
      },
      {
        "front": "javelin throw",
        "back": "rzut oszczepem"
      },
      {
        "front": "pole vault",
        "back": "skok o tyczce"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "EN-PL proffesions",
    "cards": [
      {
        "front": "lawyer",
        "back": "prawnik"
      },
      {
        "front": "truck driver",
        "back": "kierowca ciężarówki"
      },
      {
        "front": "surgeon",
        "back": "chirurg"
      },
      {
        "front": "teacher",
        "back": "nauczyciel"
      },
      {
        "front": "accountant",
        "back": "księgowy"
      },
      {
        "front": "software engineer",
        "back": "programista"
      },
      {
        "front": "waiter",
        "back": "kelner"
      },
      {
        "front": "baker",
        "back": "piekarz"
      },
      {
        "front": "prosecutor",
        "back": "prokurator"
      },
      {
        "front": "solicitor",
        "back": "radca prawny"
      },
      {
        "front": "urzędnik",
        "back": "clerk"
      }
    ]
  }
]
